Privacy Policy
--------------

We have prepared this Privacy Notice to explain how, why, and when we collect data from you on our website.

Please note that this Privacy Notice only applies to data that we collect when you visit the Tuxler website at [https://tuxlervpn.com](https://www.tuxlervpn.com/).

About Tuxler’s Services

Tuxler provides targeted advertising services for our advertiser clients (“Advertisers”). When you visit a website operated by an Advertiser or a third party site where we could serve an ad to you, we may collect some or all of the data described in the Tuxler Service Privacy Notice. Our platform uses that data as well as other data described below to help Advertisers provide ads to you that are more relevant to you.

For example, if you visit an Advertiser’s website and shop for running shoes, our Platform may later serve you with targeted ads for the Advertiser’s brand of running shoes as you browse the internet.

What data we collect and how we use it

We may collect the following categories of information on our website and use them for the purposes explained below.

* **Website activity:** Data about your browsing activity on our website
* **Device and browser information:** Technical information about the device or browser you use to access our website. For example, your device’s IP address, and (in the case of mobile devices) your device type and mobile device’s unique identifier such as the Apple IDFA or Android Advertising ID.
* **Contact Information:** If you choose to provide your name, email address or phone number
* **Account Information:** If you open a account, we will collect your username and a password and other information to necessary to open and access your account
* **Customer Service Information:** Information you may provide to customer service including survey responses
* **Financial Information:** Credit card number or other payment account information. This information is collected directly by our payments processor and not stored at Tuxler.
* **Third party information:** We may collect additional information about you from third party sources where we have the rights to do so.

We use this data to:

* provide Tuxler services and customer support
* collect fees and troubleshoot problems
* prevent potential fraud and enforce our Terms of Service
* customize, measure, and improve our website and services
* deliver targeted marketing to you
* contact you by email or phone about your account or our services including to market our services to you

Data Sharing

We may disclose personally identifying information (PII) about you:

* **With our service providers:** Companies we contract with who help with parts of our business operations. We require that our service providers only use your PII in connection with the services they perform for us.
* **With your service providers:** Companies under contract with, or acting on your behalf, who handle data (such as a customer lists) on your behalf.
* **With our subsidiaries and related companies**
* **In connection with legal proceedings:** When we are under a legal obligation to do so, for example to comply with a binding order of a court, or where disclosure is necessary to exercise, establish or defend the legal rights of Tuxler, our Advertisers or any other third party.
* **In connection with a sale of our business:** If a third party acquires some or all of our business or assets, we may disclose your PII in connection with the sale.

We also share technical data that we collect about your browsing habits and your device (such as data relating to our cookies, tracking pixels and similar technologies) with other advertising companies in the digital advertising ecosystem. This enables them and us to better target ads to you.

Finally, we may disclose aggregated, anonymized information to our Advertisers and other third parties.

Cookies and related technologies

The Tuxler website uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies. Cookies are small data files that are served by our platform and stored on your device. Our site uses cookies dropped by us or third parties for a variety of purposes including to operate and personalize the website. Also, cookies may also be used to track how you use the site to target ads to you on other websites.

To get more information about the individual cookies dropped by our website, please see the Adjust Ad Preferences link on the footer of our website.

Data retention

PII is held no longer than necessary for our business purposes or to meet legal requirements.

General Data Protection Regulation

Effective : May 25th, 2018  
Our nex privacy Policy has been updated in order to fully comply to GDPR.

We are proud to announce that our company complies with the EU regulation regarding data protection. We have always been concerned about data protection in our company. Please read our privacy Policy in order to to understand how we collect data and what we do with it.   
If there is a conflict between our privacy Policy and GDPR, you should consider that GDPR will prevail over our terms. We want to make sure that you feel protected as one of our customers.

To view/remove data we collected go to: [https://www.tuxlervpn.com/view-collected-data/](https://www.tuxlervpn.com/view-collected-data/)  
If you want to make another GPRD related request please use form at: [https://www.tuxlervpn.com/gprd-request/](https://www.tuxlervpn.com/gdpr-request/)

Security

We apply technical, administrative and organizational security measures to protect the data we collect against accidental or unlawful destruction and loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, in particular where the processing involves the transmission of data over a network, and against other unlawful forms of processing.

Changes to this Privacy Notice

Changes to this Privacy Notice will be posted on this page. If we make a material change to our privacy practices, we will provide notice on the site or by other means as appropriate.

Contact us about questions or concerns

If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice, our privacy practices, or with Tuxler generally, you can contact **support@tuxler.com.**
